嘿，下午好，为什么我们不一起做一个
hey good afternoon so why don't we do a
模组，这样你就可以
mod together just so that you get the
感受到我
feel for maybe the new uh way I'm kind
处理模型的新方式，然后
of working on models and then
看看我实际上是怎么做的，
see how actually I kind of do it and
然后看看你是否想要 采用我的一些
then see if you want to adopt some of my
方法，
methods
所以我想做的是重新审视一个旧的，一个
so what I want to do is revisit an old
我已经
uh an older one I've kind of been
研究了一段时间的旧方法，看看我是否可以
working on a while and see if I can
改进它一点点，
improve on it a little bit
嗯，这基本上就是
um which is essentially the White Queen
我要的白皇后 我的一生都在努力，
I to my whole life kind of been working
就像
on like
几个月前一样，感觉已经很久了，但让我们
months ago it feels like ages but let's
看看我们如何尝试改进这
see how we could try to improve this
件事，让它实际上变得更好，嗯，
thing so that it actually is a better uh
更好的模型，
a better model
所以首先我要创建一个
so first thing I'm gonna go and create a
新文件夹 时不时地，我将
new folder here and then and I'm going
复制所有这些图像，以便我
to copy all of those image such that I
有一个我们可以编辑的工作副本，所以
have a working copy that we can edit so
我将创建一个新文件夹，我
I'm going to create a new folder I'm
将调用它
going to call that
可以图像 V2
can image V2
然后我是 要
and then I'm gonna
复制我在这里得到的所有这些图像，
copy all of those image that I've got
包括标题
here including the captions
我要将所有这些东西复制到
I'm going to copy all that stuff into
图像 YouTube 文件夹中，
the image YouTube folder
然后在该文件夹中我将
and within that folder I'm going to
创建另一个文件夹，我将
create another folder that I'm going to
调用新
call new
文件夹 我打算称之为
folder I'm going to call that
is
Raw
我将把所有这些图像拆分成
I'm going to split all of those image in
there
关于那是我的鸟的故事，它
story about that that's my bird that's
有点疯狂所以我不确定
kind of going nuts so I'm not sure if
你是否能在录音中听到它但
you can hear it on the recording but
也许是 你想知道那是什么 那是
maybe so if you wonder what that was
我的小鹦鹉 它在
that's my little parrot that's kind of
楼下咯咯地叫
uh squawking down downstairs
所以我有所有这些图像
so uh so I've got all those image so
所以我们有一个观点让我们把它们
just so we have a view let's bring them
带上来 你真正想做的一件事
up and one thing that you really want to
呃 当你有 像那样的图像和
do uh when you have image like that and
我学到的一件事我学到了很多是你
one thing I've I've learned a lot is you
真的需要专注于主题所以
really need to focus on the subject so
摆脱任何不是呃
get rid of anything that does not uh
那不是主题并且会
that is not the subject and that will
丢掉学习的东西所以我们要
throw the learning away so we're gonna
必须去编辑所有这些图像以
have to go and edit all those image to
稍微清理它们所以
kind of clean them up a little bit so
我要在这里启动 Photoshop
I'm going to fire up Photoshop here and
我要带来第一张图像是的
I'm going to bring the first image
我们需要做一些
and yeah we're going to need to do some
裁剪 为了控制这个主要主题，
cropping just to keep that main subject
所以我们要
in check so we're just going to go and
删除很多内容，
remove a lot of the content
是的，我的分辨率不是很好，我
and yeah my resolution is not so great I
看到我会像一些 sub
see that I'm gonna have like some sub
500 和 512 x 512 分辨率
500 and 512 by 512 resolution
um
嗯是的 那会很棒，但
yeah that's that's going to be great but
我想我们只是在
I guess we're just going to go with what
某个时候使用我们现有的东西，现在你必须使用
we've got sometime now you've got to use
你所拥有的东西，这将
what you've got this one is going to be
再次变得相当小，
like fairly small again
肯定是一些我不会的东西' 不
definitely some what I wouldn't
建议像你不想做
recommend like you don't want to go
任何小于 512 x 512 的东西，否则
anything less than 512 by 512 otherwise
你会遇到麻烦，但
you get into trouble
我想在这种情况下我会有
but I guess in this case I'm gonna have
很多选择，
much choice
我会继续编辑那个，
and I'm Gonna Keep Going edit that one
所以请检查一下 我们只是添加
so bring it in check so we just add the
主题 Focus 因为那是
subject Focus because that's where the
学习将要发生的地方，
learning is going to take place right
保留所有这些东西是没有意义的
there's no point in keeping all of that
因为那不是我们
stuff around because that's not what we
想要学习的我只想了解
want to learn I just want to learn about
一个主题而不是其他所以我' 我
the one subject and nothing else so I'm
只是继续前进，即使
just going to keep going and even though
它们很小，它仍然会
those are quite small it will still add
为模型添加有价值的信息，它们
valuable information to the model they
只是在训练过程中学习的更小的
will just be smaller kind of learned
部分，
parts
during the training
所以我们将保留我们将
so we're going to keep the hands we're
要使用的手 空气的背面
going to go with the back of the air and
听起来不错让我们保留那个
that sounds good let's keep that one
我要继续并保持手
I'm gonna go ahead and keep the hand
在这里
here
只是砍掉左右不相关的东西
just chop what's not relevant on the
所以我只是快速
left and right so I'm just quickly going
通过这里
through here
保持手
keeping the hands
砍疯帽匠 有点在这个
chopping the Mad Hatter sort of in the
过程中，
process
如果那个模型结果很好，我
and if that model turns out good I'm
会把它发布在
going to publish it on
civit AI 上，所以
civit AI so
现在我有一大堆
now I've got a whole bunch of image that
重复的图像，所以可能会证明
are repetitive so that could prove like
部分有问题，它可能会
partially problematic it might
像学习过程一样触发 可能
trigger like the learning process might
会歪斜所以这个很软但是
get skewed so this one is quite soft but
哦好吧我们可以尝试看看我们是否可以
oh well we can try to see if we can fix
通过某种方式修复它所以这个所以这个
it in some ways so this this so this one
所以现在我要展示其中
so now I'm kind of going to show like
一些
some of those are pretty much well
裁剪得很好 这个需要一些非常
cropped this one needs some very
裁剪，而
cropping
不是我所说的完全腐败的
not what I would call perfectly corrupt
主题，
subject
我们只是去关注
we're just going to go and focus on the
这里的一个主题，
one subject here
让我们
make that
继续
going
看图像的其余部分，
kind of looking at the rest of the image
他们再次非常腐败，只是
they are pretty well corrupt again just
看看那些 那些有一个裁剪
looking at those ones there's a cropping
我可以进一步裁剪那个
I could crop that one a little further
所以我们摆脱不是那样
so we get rid of not that way
保存这个
save this one
以裁剪这个
to crop this one
很好我想我们有肉汤不错它
well I guess we have broth not bad it
可能只是底部有太多东西
might just there's too much stuff at the
直到我们可以删除
bottom here until we can remove there is
模型没有什么可学的，所以
nothing to learn there for the model so
这甚至不会浪费那些像素我正在
that's not even waste those pixels I'm
学习无关紧要的东西
learning stuff that doesn't matter
呃快速经历
uh quickly going through
快速增长好吧让我
quickly growing through well let me
暂停视频我要去
pause the video and I'm gonna go and
修改所有这些 然后我们再次成为它
modify all of them and then we're again
完成的原因
the reason when it's done
所以我几乎所有的
okay so I've got pretty much all of the
图像都按照我想要的方式损坏所以我们
image corrupt the way I want so we have
喜欢周围正确构图的
like properly framed
主题
subject all around
所以我在这个阶段可能想做的
so what I might want to do at this stage
是尝试 看看我是否可以
is try to see if I can improve
稍微改善这些图像以获得
these image a little bit to get like
更干净的面孔，因为其中一些有
cleaner faces because some of them have
一些
kind of
嘈杂的面孔，但不是很好 有时它们
noisy not so great Faces Sometimes they
有点模糊
are kind of a little bit uh blurry and
等等，让我们看看我们是否不能
whatnot so let's see if we could not
改善那又怎样 我要做的是
improve that so what I'm going to do is
我要在这里复制这张
I'm going to copy here the path to this
图片的路径，然后我将一个一个地进入自动模式
image and I'm going to go into Auto one
one one
，我将进入附加功能，
and I'm going to go under the extras and
我将进入批次模式 从
I'm going to go under batch from
目录中加载我的
directory and I'm going to load my
文件夹我将把
folder here I'm going to put
第二个作为 Gan 将
the second one as Gan so I'm going to
process all of those image and just for
a good measure I'm going to resize all
它们的分辨率也加倍，
of them to double their resolution as
所以我们将
well so we're gonna double up the
每张图像的分辨率加倍，然后我
resolution of each image and then I'm
将对每张调整大小的图像运行完整的 gan
going to run a full gan
呃清理
uh clean up on each of these resized
以尝试提高面部质量
image to try to improve the quality of
the faces
所以我们不显示 结果，但
so let's not show the results but for
现在我们只是要去，
now we're just gonna go and
嗯，
um
对所有图像都这样做，这是
do that for all of the image now the one
我将要处理的一个问题，这是一个
issue that I'm gonna have and that's a
挑战，过程如何进行，
challenge with how the process goes and
也许我不会这样做，因为
maybe I'm not going to do it because of
我所有的图像都被重述了，
that all of my image are all recaptioned
我有很短的标题，上面
where I've got like very short captions
写着白皇后，你知道
that says the White Queen you know what
我们可能会放弃它，
maybe we're just going to ditch that and
我们只是
we're just going to go with something
为这个演示做一些基本的事情所以 让我们甚至不
basic for this demo so let's not even
关心我得到的那些字幕，
care about those captions that I've got
因为它们是超级基本的，本质上只是
because they are super basic just
主题的名称，
essentially it's the name of the subject
有时
and sometime when there's uh
甚至在这种情况下也没有，就像有时我
not even in this case like sometimes I
有它，就像是否有皇冠一样
had had it like if there was a crown or
但是 让我们什至不理会它
not but let's not even bother with that
所以让我们跳过让我们忘记
so let's just skip that let's forget
它并且让我们运行这个呃
about it and let's kind of run this uh
放大并清理实际的
upscaling and clean up of the actual
面孔让我们看看会发生什么所以现在
faces and let's see what happens so now
如果我去这里应该有
if I go here there should be
一个应该显示的新文件夹 当
a new folder that should show up when
Gan 开始正常运行时，
Gan starts to run
all right
它正在生成，
so it's generating
所以它应该显示为两个原始图像，所以
so it should show up as image two raw so
它应该在这里，
it should be in here
现在我们应该开始看到图像
and now we should start to see the image
作为清理后的图像出现，如果我们看
coming up as cleaned up image if we look
它们，也许脸是
at them maybe the face is a little bit
这里有点太干净了，我们并没有丢失
too clean here there's not we've lost a
很多面部细节，所以也许
lot of the details of the face so maybe
这有点太强了，
this is a little too strong
只是有点太强了，但有时它
just a tad too strong but sometimes it
可以帮助学习整个模型，
could help learning the whole model
因为现在图像少了很多
because now the image is a lot less
嘈杂，
noisy
呃，你知道我们要做什么，
uh you know what we're going to go with
我们要用那种
that we're going to go with that kind of
力量去清洁面部
a strength of cleaning up of the face
，也许结果会很好，
and maybe it's going to turn out good
也许不会那么好，
maybe it's not going to be so good and
我们” 你将需要再次用较低的重做它，
we're going to need to redo it with
但
lower again but
它让你知道你可以做些什么来
it gives you an idea of what you can do
清理面部，所以你可以从
to clean up faces so you can go from
看起来让我们看看我是否可以带来
as looking let's see if I can bring like
一张简短的实际之前的脸，让我们
a face that's a brief pre-actual uh
看看 以
let's look at
这个为例，
this one for example
这就是清理前的样子
so that's what it looks like before the
，让我们带来
cleanup and let's bring what it looks
清理后的样子，因为无论如何我都必须
like after the cleanup because I've got
等待它完成，
to wait anyway for it to complete
所以这是清理后的新版本
so this is the new version after a
，这是升级后的版本
cleanup and this is the upscaling and
这是清理和放大之前的版本，
this is the version before clean up and
所以你可以看到
upscaling so you can see that there's a
lot less
它可能对我们不利的瑕疵少了很多，
blemishes it might be working against us
但它确实在头发中添加了很多细节
but it does add a lot of details in the
并且很好地放大了一些东西所以
hair and scaling up things quite well so
它应该有助于学习
it should help with the learning of the
实际的劳拉，
actual Laura
所以是的，这是我过去
so yeah so that's a process I used to
实际上
actually get a better picture
通过放大然后用
for training by just upscaling and then
cleaning them up with the
我想用 gan 清理它们来获得更好的训练图片的过程
I guess with gan
所以我要暂停，直到我们
so I'm going to pause until we have all
清理了所有图像并且 我不会
the image cleaned up and I'm not going
继续，这样我就不会让你
to resume so that I don't get you to
浪费时间看油漆干了
waste your time watching paint dry
好吧感谢编辑的魔力现在
okay thanks to the magic of editing now
所有的图片都已经放大所以
all the pictures have been upscaled so
下一步是检查所有
the next step is to go through all of
这些并确保 没有
them and make sure there's no bad
我们想要丢弃的坏照片，所以让我们
pictures that we want to discard so
一张一张地看它们，一个
let's go and look them one by one that
很好，一个很酷，很好，一个很好，嗯，
one's fine that one's cool that's fine
好的，好的，很好，很好，很好，很好，很好，
that one is okay uh okay okay yeah
that's good that's good
fine fine
很好，
okay good good that one sort of view
从 后面这个有点
from the back this one is kind of uh
模糊不太好所以让我们
blurry all around not good so let's
删除它
delete it
嗯那会很好很好很好你看到
uh that would be good good good you see
后面没关系
the back that's okay it's always good to
听到一个主题总是很好
have you heard a subject that one is
sort of
我不知道让我们 删除它呃
yeah I don't know let's delete it uh
这个更好更好好吧
this one is better better
okay
好吧你能预订所有好的那个
okay can you book all good that one's a
从后面看的风景
view from the back
嗯
um
我想我不知道它增加了很多
I guess I don't know that it adds much
所以让我们删除它
so let's delete it
uh
呃是的那个不是很好我认为
yeah that one's not very good I think
脸不 看起来不太好 呃
the face doesn't look good uh it's kind
从后面看有点模糊 没关系
of blurry view from the back that's okay
okay
look good look good look good
yeah yeah
that one not so great so I still need it
好吧 看起来不错
that one's okay okay okay okay okay
and that's it now let's make sure there
没有任何问题，就像我注意到的那样，
is no issues with any like I've noticed
当它有点升级时，我
when it was kind of upscaling that I've
得到了这样的图像，例如，它是
got like this one for example is kind of
另一个图像的反转图像，所以这个
a reverse image of the other one so this
图像
one is sort of
是它还是不是它是反转的 我
is it or is it not is it reverse I'm
看到了锅碗瓢盆，我看到了一些
seeing pots and pans and I'm seeing kind
相同的东西，
of the same
所有的一切，它看起来像
and all and everything it looks like
这个，就像一个反转的图像，也许
this one is like a reverse image maybe
当是的，也许
when the
它就像反转一样，
yeah maybe it's just like the reversal
让我们​​删除其中一个，我
let's delete one of them which one do I
想要哪个 为了保留，我认为我有很多
want to keep I think I've got plenty of
面孔，但侧面较少，所以我要
face but fewer of the side so I'm going
删除那个，
to delete that one
呃，任何其他跳跃的东西，
uh anything else that kind of jumps this
我认为这很好，它们是
one I think is fine those are two sides
同一个人的两个侧面，所以她有点 旋转
of the same person so she kind of spun
一下，这样没关系，
around so that's okay
嗯，我认为其他一切看起来都还
uh I think everything else looks
不错，所以我认为我们
okay-ish so I think we're pretty much
对这个数据集非常满意，它会给
good with this data set which would give
我们大约
us about
30 47 个图像，
30 47 image
嗯，
um
这不是完美的数字 48
which is not the perfect number 48 would
会更好，因为它更多 一个可被
have been better because it's more of a
4 整除的数字 呃，也许
a divisible number by four uh what maybe
我们需要修剪一些，以便我们
we need to trim a few just so that we
得到一个可以被 4 整除的数字，
get to a number that can be divisible by
例如 44
4 like 44 for example
嗯，所以让我们尝试减少三个图像
um so let's try to cut down three image
，我们有很多重复
and we have quite a bit of repetitions
在这个系列中，所以也许我们可以在那里剪掉其中一个，
in this series so maybe we can cut one
of them there
所以这个看起来不一样，这个
so this one is looking different this
非常严重，所以也许我们剪掉了，
one is serious serious so maybe we cut
也许我们剪掉了，
maybe we cut
我不知道这个或那个
I don't know this one or that one
让我们剪掉这个，
let's cut this one
现在我们要 [
now we're down to 46. uh what else could
we remove
think that
we could probably do away with maybe one
of those
one does not much value
there's no face presence so let's delete
that one
um
now we need to cut one more which is
going to get cut
音乐]  ]
[Music]
是的，我们几乎有一个双倍的，
yeah here we almost have like a double
所以看起来它们是不同的，但它们
so it looks like they are different but
是双倍的，所以这个她
they are doubled so this one she's got
闭上了眼睛这个，
the eyes closed this one
嗯，
um
我认为这个是正确的一面，
I think this one is the right side this
这个是错误的一面，所以我要走了
one is the wrong side so I'm going to
剪切错误的侧面图像好吧，现在我们已经
cut the wrong side image okay now we're
下降到 44。我们在一个好地方
down to 44. we're in a good place
好吧，所以现在我们
okay so now that that's done what we
需要做的是，即使我们
need to do is even though we could
可能不带标题也可以取消，我
probably do away without caption what I
想做的是标题 图像
want to do is caption the image such
使得我们有一些
that we have like
东西会说出一个独特的
something that's going to say a unique
关键字，而不是白皇后，因为
keyword like not the White Queen because
它在稳定的传播中是众所周知的，
it's kind of known within a stable
所以我宁愿使用
diffusion so I would rather use more
更像一个梦幻靴子令牌，它是独一无二的，
like a dream boot token that is unique
就像来自 名字
like just the few letters from the name
，然后是一些
and then something that also gonna go
我们希望呃
and describe things that we want the uh
系统忘记的东西，比如在这种
system to sort of forget like in this
情况下，她戴着她的王冠，她没有
case she's wearing her crown she's not
戴她的王冠，所以我想做的
wearing her crown so what I want to do
是把王冠当作一个可选的东西，
is have the crown like an optional thing
所以我 我要在舞会上告诉 stable diffusion
so I'm going to tell stable diffusion in
她在这张照片上戴着皇冠，
a prom that she's wearing a crown on
而在这张照片中我不
this picture and in this one I'm not
打算说明，因为她
going to State it because she doesn't
没有皇冠
have a crown
我还看到有一些图像
I also see that there is some image
她拿着一个 剑 所以我要
where she's holding a sword so I'm going
在那些图片的字幕中加上
to put sword in those captions for those
剑 我要在
ones and I'm gonna put swords in uh
没有剑的地方放剑
where there's no swords I'm just going
to go ahead and do a quick captioning of
each image and then we're going to get
当它通过编辑的魔力完成时回来
back when it's done through the magic of
editing
哦
oh
为什么我不告诉你我
why don't I show you uh that how I
实际上是如何做一个快速字幕
actually go and do a quick captioning
我将使用 Koya SS GUI 我将
I'm going to use Koya SS GUI I'm gonna
进入实用程序并且我' 我只是
go under the utilities and I'm just
要进入呃基本字幕我
gonna go under uh basic captioning I'm
要放入包含图像的实际文件夹，
gonna put the actual folder that
在
contains the image which would be in
这种情况下是地毯罐文件夹
this case the rug can folder
我要复制
I'm going to copy that
我要去这里把它放到
I'm going to go here put that into
这里的部分所以 我想获取文本文件
section here so I want to get text file
我想覆盖任何现有的
I want to overwrite any existing
说明文字，因为我需要做
captions because I'm going to need to do
一些事情，所以首先我
a couple things so first thing I'm going
要为每张图片加上白皇后的说明文字，
to go and caption each image with
the White Queen so t h e w h i t e q u
e
这样白皇后就
so the White Queen
这样了 这应该可以解决白
so so that should do the trick the White
皇后的问题，好吧，所以我要用它作为
Queen okay so I'm going to use that as
标题文本，所以我要为
the caption text so I'm going to caption
每张图片加上标题，我要删除这里的任何内容，
each image I'm going to delete anything
这样就可以了，
here so by doing that it's going and
它会创建一个
it's going to create a caption text file
包含第一个关键字的标题文本文件现在我
that contains that first keyword now I
注意到我应该放一个逗号
noticed that I should have put a comma
因为有逗号很好
because it's nice to have commas there's
当你学习模型时有一个很好的技巧
a nice trick when you learn the model
关于逗号所以我要做的
with about comma so what I'm going to do
是我要去 摆脱这个，我
is I'm going to get rid of this and I'm
要把它放到查找文本框中
going to put that into the find text box
，我想用
and I want to replace this with a the
末尾带逗号的白皇后替换它，所以
White Queen with the comma at the end so
如果我点击标题，我会回到这里
if I hit caption and I come back here
，现在如果我打开一个 又一次
and now if I open one of them again
你会看到我们
you're going to see now that we have the
在末尾有逗号，这很好，
comma at the end which is good now with
我将不得不去手动
that I'm gonna have to go and manually
打开一个一个，呃，她
open one by one uh the ones where she
有皇冠的那些，所以现在我会去 在这张照片中，
has it Crown so now I would go in this
我要说的是皇冠类型，
one I'm going to say type crown
因为她在这张照片中有一顶皇冠
because she's got a crown in this
，我想把这个关键字添加
picture and I want to add that keyword
到她戴着它的每一张照片中，
to every picture where she is wearing it
所以我现在要保存这个我需要在
brown so I'm gonna save this now I need
技术上进入每一个 其中之一
to technically go in every one of them
并添加该关键字所以我要
and add that keyword so I'm going to
暂停它所以我要添加皇冠并且
pause this so I'm going to add crown and
我要添加剑到
I'm going to add sword to the ones that
我想要的那些然后这就是
I want and then that's going to be it
for the captioning
我认为看到的字幕 现在已经完成了字幕，
I think saw a captioning is done so now
如果你看这个，例如，
if you look at this one for example
我们有带剑的白皇后，
we've got the White Queen with the sword
如果我们看那个，我们有带
if we look at that one we've got the
皇冠的白皇后，所以这就是
white queen with the crown so this is
你如何完成所有的 字幕
how you get through all of the captions
呃，你有点列出了
uh and you're kind of listing the
每张图片的独特元素，这些元素
elements that are unique to it each
不属于该主题，
image that are not part of that subject
但实际上是
but that are actually kind of addition
它的补充，就像一把剑和一顶王冠，所以现在
to it like a sword and a crown so now
已经完成了，呃，我们需要什么
that that's done uh what do we need to
现在下一步我们需要继续并开始
do next now we need to go ahead and
配置我们将如何训练
start to configure how we're gonna train
这个东西所以如果我回到
this thing so if I go back to in image
这里的图像看到我们有两个文件夹
here see we do we have got two folders
四个
four
um
嗯 Koya 说要正确训练这些
uh Koya says to properly train on these
我们 需要有一个
ones we need to have a single folder
包含图像的文件夹，所以我将
that contains the image so I'm going to
在这里创建一个新文件夹，我将其
create a new one here that I'm going to
命名为
call
嗯，
um
我将其命名为什么，所以也许我
I'm going to call it what so maybe I
可以使用我正在使用的原始 Gan 文件夹
could just use the raw Gan folder I'm
只是要在其中创建子文件夹，
just going to create the subfolder
within it
鉴于图像的数量，我将重复 50 次，
and I'm going to do 50 repeats given the
也许 50 次就
number of image maybe 50 is going to be
足够了，所以重复 50 次，我将
good enough so 50 repeats and I'm gonna
输入
put
我们得到的关键字，以便我们
the keyword that we've got so that we
知道 这是关键字 所以 th
know that this is the keyword so th
h t
w h t
立方体
cubed
u-e-e-n 所以白皇后
u-e-e-n so the White Queen
我要去这里 选择所有
I'm gonna go down here select all the
文件并将所有这些文件移动到
files and move all those files inside
该文件夹​​中
that folder
所以现在我们有了它并且我们有了地图 我们
so now we have that and we have a map we
应该有一个匹配的
should have a matching
工具包 t h w h t q n excellent 所以
toolkit right t h w h t q n excellent so
让我们匹配它好吧，既然已经完成了，
let's match it okay now that that's done
我们可以复制
we can copy
this
这个文件夹名称，
this folder name
然后我们可以进入 Koya SS GUI 并
and then we can go into Koya SS GUI and
进入 dream boot Laura，我们
go under dream boot Laura and we're
将开始
gonna start
创造这个传说，所以我要做的第一件事
to create this lore so first thing I'm
做的是重用现有的参数我
gonna do is reuse existing parameters I
猜我刚刚
had for I guess the training I was just
做的训练所以我将用
doing so I'm going to replace this with
我的图像路径替换它在这种情况下我做了
the path for my image in this case I did
一个设置白皇后图像 V2 rugan
a set the White Queen image V2 rugan
我只是要去 去复制
and I'm just going to go and copy and
你知道我想要什么我通常把劳拉
you know what I want I usually put Laura
放在那里因为我想区分
in there because I want to differentiate
劳拉和文本倒置的数据集
data sets for Laura and textual
我要去这里然后去
inversions I'm going to go here and just
修复我要
going to go and fix I'm going to fix
在这里修复我 我只是要去创建
that here I'm just going to go create
一个新文件夹 我要打电话给劳拉
a new folder I'm going to call Laura
我得把这个扔到那里
and I Gotta Throw This one there and
我要抓取我的
that's where I'm going to grab my
图像
image
所以回到这里替换它 所以现在
so going back here replacing that so now
我们有了劳拉 现在是什么 我能做的
we have the Laura and now what I can do
是我可以去替换我对项目
is I can go and replace all of my
文件夹的所有现有引用
existing reference to the folder
所以现在我们很好所以
for the project so now we're good so
我们接下来要做的实际上是
what we want to do next is actually
在稳定中创建一个文件夹我
create a folder in the stable where I'm
将把我的稳定 扩散
going to put my stable diffusion
学习，这将成为
learning that's so that's going to be
模型的输出，所以我将
the output for the model so I'm going to
其称为
call it
为什么
why
Queen
和瓶子的名称将与
and the name of the bottle is going to
我们目前拥有的实际标记相匹配，
match the actual token that we have for
所以如果我回到这里，
the moment so if I go back here
呃
uh
选择 在这里，所以标记是
select this here so the token is
that
回到哦，是的，我要把它
going back to oh yeah I'm gonna put that
作为我的
as my
开场白，我要创建
opening and I'm going to create e
第一个电子版本，我要复制这个东西
version one I'm going to copy this thing
，我要把它作为我的
and I'm going to put that as my
配置 文件名所以我知道它是否
configuration file name so I knew it if
是配置文件，让我们保存它
this was to config and let's save it
让我们确保它确实保存了文件而
let's make sure it did save the file
没有任何错误所以我要
without any error so to do that I'm just
进去看看这是它
going to go in and see this is where it
说保存没有错误的地方 所以我们
said save there was no error so we're
很好地保存了
good with the saving
嗯
um
我想我真的不再需要
I guess I really don't really need a
在那里发表评论所以我们很好地
comment in there anymore so we're good
保存了那部分
with that that that that part is saved
我们现在有了配置
we have the configuration now the
参数这是
parameters this is where it's
有趣的地方所以 我正在使用 呃 我
interesting right so I'm using uh I
想在这种情况下 44 的批量大小
guess in this case batch size of a 44 is
不会被 8 整除所以
not going to be divisible by eight so
这会导致一些问题 44
that's going to cause some issue 44
除以 8 等于 5.5 所以我说是的
divided by 8 equal 5.5 so I said yeah
嗯我想我会做四个我' 我打算
um I think I will just do four I'm going
做四批，这样 44 就可以被
to do batches of four so that 44 is
8 整除 4，
totally divisible by eight by four and
它会给出 11
it's going to give 11
基本上是 11 组四张图像，所以
essentially 11 groups of four image so
我要训练批量大小为 4
I'm going to do train batch size of four
呃，我们要训练一个 Epoch 我们
uh we're gonna train for one Epoch we
有一个名为文本的字幕扩展名，
have a caption extension called the text
我们将在我的案例中使用我将
we're gonna do in my case I'm gonna do
混合 Precision BF 50 16 进行培训，
mix Precision BF 50 16 for the training
但我将保存在 fp16 中以
but I'm Gonna Save in fp16 for
与那里的用户兼容，
compatibility for users out there
嗯学习率这是我的东西 我
um learning rate this is something I'm
不会设置，因为我正在使用
not gonna set because I'm kind of using
一个特殊版本的 uh
a special version of uh the trainer that
我得到的训练器，它正在使用一种叫做
I've got which is using something called
uh
all right 动态适应的东西，它
all right Dynamic adaptation which is
会为我计算学习率，
going to calculate the learning rate for
所以我不会去 现在必须指定
me so I'm not going to have to specify
学习权限的程度
the learning right degree right now
在那个版本中仍然有字段，
still has the fields when in that
但这没关系，因为
version but that's okay because that's
如果你要在没有动态适应的情况下进行训练，那将被忽略，
going to be ignored if you are to train
那么这些值
without Dynamic adaptation then those
将是很好的开始值，比如
would be good values to start like zero
零零零一个是 对训练有很好的价值，
zero zero one is a good value for
有趣的是，
training and interestingly enough most
大多数时候动态适应
of the time Dynamic adaptation kind of
接近这个值并且它保持
gets close to this value and it stays
在那里并且它提供了相当好的
there and it provides pretty good
结果
results
嗯再次学习率调度器
um again that learning rate scheduler is
不会被使用它会被
not going to be used it's going to be
忽略
ignored
嗯我' 我不会迟到兑现，
um I'm not going to cash late and
因为我要向你展示
because I'm going to show you something
我在培训期间要做的事情，所以
that I'm gonna do during the training so
我将创建一个 128 级的 uh Laura
I'm going to create a 128 rank uh Laura
512 by 5 哲学解决方案我
512 by 5 philosophy solution I want
绝对想启用存储桶，因为
definitely to enable buckets because
我 我在高级配置侧令牌填充中得到了一个混合纵横比数据
I've got like a mixed aspect ratio data
集
set
um
um in the advanced config side
可以使用创建的
token padding that can use that created
累积步骤一个很好之前的
accumulation steps one that's fine prior
损失重量一个学习率
loss weight one learning rate number of
循环数我没有做多个呃时代
Cycles I'm not doing multiple uh epochs
所以不会 重要的是象征性的
so that doesn't matter keep in token
嗯
um
我想要我真的不想像
I want I don't really want to enforce
第一个看到的那样强制执行并且一直在
like the first to look and to be
开始所以我
at the beginning all the time so I don't
不在乎剪辑跳过我发现把它
care clip skip I found that leaving it
留给一个人对实际的人类
to one does better with actual human
角色更好 令牌长度是的 75 我们
characters token length yeah 75 we don't
不需要更改那个乱序的字幕，
need to change that shuffled captions
因为我有几个
because I've got like a couple of
字幕，
captions like where something that it's
就像它是
like it's kind of the word for the
主题和皇冠或剑的词，我要把
subject and Crown or sword I'm gonna
字幕这样洗牌 它们可以
Shuffle the caption such that they could
颠倒它们可以以不同的
be reversed they can come in different
顺序出现所以这是一个很好的做法我
orders so that's a good practice I'm
会做我不再使用 8 位空闲
gonna do I'm not using 8-bit idle
因为我发现它给出的
anymore because I find that it gives
结果比你实际上
worse result than when you actually
不使用它时更糟糕所以我 我要花点时间
don't use it so I'm taking a bit out and
使用 x formers 是的颜色增强
out use x formers yes color augmentation
没有翻转增强不因为它是一个
no flip augmentation no because it's a
人，翻转会有点
human and flipping will kind of enforce
像奇怪的人工制品一样强制执行因为它会让
like weird artifacts because it's going
这个主题它会让它
to make this subject it's going to make
学会成为一个善良的主题 的
it learn to be a subject with kind of
对称特征，但人类
symmetrical features but humans are
从来都不是真正对称的，所以最好
never really symmetrical so it's better
保留它，因为人类没有解决
to leave it up for humans don't have
方案的比例桶在我们的例子中，
scale buckets with Solutions in our case
这无关紧要，因为我们的
it's not going to matter because we have
图像大于 512 x 512，所以如果我们
image bigger than 512 by 512 so if we
有更小的图像 不要升级
had smaller image that don't upscale
会让它们变小，而不是将
would keep them small instead of
它们升级到
upscaling them up
桶分辨率步骤，这是一个
bucket resolution steps this is an
有趣的，
interesting one
嗯，
um
你可以降到 16 或 32。
you could go down to like 16 or 32.
在我的情况下，我将在 16 时尝试。所以
in my case I'm going to try it at 16. so
我要 执行第 16 步的桶分辨率。
I'm going to do bucket resolution step
所以这就是说，
16. so what that says is that an image
如果图像不完全符合分辨率，则可以将其裁剪 16 个像素，
can be cropped by 16 pixels if it
doesn't perfectly fit in the resolution
嗯，这是 16 的倍数，将被
uh that's a multiple of 16 that's going
计算为接近 512 x
to get calculated to be close to 512 by
512，并且 然后是
512 and then total number of pixels
um
实际帮助随机
that is actually helping with the random
裁剪而不是中心裁剪选项的总像素数
crop instead of Center crop option that
I've got here so what that does is that
every time an image is going to be
learned it's going to slightly crop it
所以它会
in a different location so it's going to
裁剪图像，所以它会对
crop the image so it's it's going to do
图像进行某种抖动，所以它
some kind of Jitter of the image so it's
会四处移动一点，如果
going to move around a little bit and if
这有助于稳定扩散，则可以
this helps stable diffusion alert the
更好地提醒模型，耳朵越大，
model better and the bigger ear the more
容量就越大 在
capacity it's going to have to crop in
不同的位置裁剪所以如果你
different locations so if you don't want
不想太大但又不想
to go too big but you don't want to go
太小所以也许我会
too small so maybe I'm going to go with
在这种情况下使用 32 所以让我们试试它作为脏
32 in this case so let's try it as dirty
um
Dropout 字幕每一个 bug 我想为
Dropout captions every any bug I want to
每个 Epoch 添加字幕，所以我不会对
caption every Epoch so I'm not going to
字幕
do any Dropout of epochs for captioning
和字幕率进行任何 Dropout Dropout 我想
and a rate of captions Dropout I want to
删除 10% 的字幕，所以在每一步
drop 10 percent of the captions so there
都有 10% 10% 的机会
is a 10 percent 10 percent chance that
caption 将被
at every step the caption is going to be
删除，这有助于为
dropped out and this is helping give the
模型提供更大的样式灵活性，因此
model more flexibility in styling so
启用 uh
it's a good option to have enabled uh
safe training State I don't really want
to do that and Max train Epoch number I
don't really want 是一个不错的选择 在我的情况下，指定
don't really want to specify and the max
数据加载器的最大工作人员数为零，
number of workers for data loader zero
我发现事情进展得更快，
in my case I find makes things go faster
所以通过将其设置为零，它有助于使
so by setting this to zero it helps make
事情变得更快，所以这是我
things faster so this is the config I've
为这次培训获得的配置，所以现在事情
got for this training so now that things
已经配置好了 我要去把
are configured I'm going to go and save
它保存到我的配置文件中，我们已经
this to my config file and we're pretty
准备好训练了，
much ready to train
um
正如我所说的，我将向你展示
as I said I'm going to show you the the
learning rate curve that is generated by
这个版本生成的学习率曲线，这是一个
this version by the way this is a
那个版本，嗯，
version that uh
我们已经到了这里，嗯，
that we've got here uh
韩国 SS，我们将进入
Korean SS we're just going to go into
代码，所以如果
the code so I've got like a branch if
你想使用它，我有一个分支，嗯，你可以去
you want to use it uh you can go and
看看学习率免费分支
look at the learning rate free branch
和这个 是
and this is where the code for the
实际学习率免费的代码所在的地方，
actual learning rate free is located
所以如果你想尝试它，
so if you want to try it that's where
你可以在那里找到它，
you could find it
所以现在让我们开始训练
okay so now let's go and start training
贸易模型，现在让我们快速查看
trade model and now let's quickly look
输出
at the output
并确保它会 开始
and make sure that it's going to start
很好，没有任何错误，
fine without any errors
所以你可以在这里看到我的
so as you can see here I've got my
桶最多包含 50 张图像，
buckets that contains up to 50 image
每个桶都有更多图像，因为
each some have more image because the
更多图片
more pictures were kind of fitted within
在裁剪后适合 512 x 512 分辨率，
this 512 by 512 resolutions after a
这将有所帮助
cropping which is going to help with
训练期间图像的抖动，
that Jitter of the image during the
现在它已经开始
training and now it's already started
训练了，我们将
training and we are going to train for
总共训练 550 步，
550 steps total
在训练期间让我们去
and while this trains let's go and grab
看看实际的日志，以便我们可以
a look at the actual logs so that we can
看到实际的学习率
see the actual learning rate in action
你会在这里开始看到
you're going to start to see here that
动态学习率 0 和
the dynamic learning rate zero and
动态学习率 1 的
dynamic learning rate one are going to
值将随着时间的推移开始增加，
start to increase in value over time
因为系统实际上是在
because the system is is actually
查看训练的结果
kind of looking at the results of the
并决定学习是否
training and deciding if the learning
应该增加速率以产生
rate should be increased to produce even
更好的结果，以便随着训练的
better results so as the training
进行，该学习率将
progress this learning rate is going to
在整个训练过程中发生变化，这
change throughout the training and this
就是动态适应的作用，它会
is what the dynamic adaptation does it
kind of calculates the training the
根据
learning rate for you based on the
每次训练的结果为您计算训练学习率 步骤
results of each training steps
所以让我们来看看
so let's go and look at the actual
包含日志的实际文件夹
folder that contains
our logs
这是包含日志的文件夹
so here this is the folder that contains
我要复制最后一条
the logs I'm going to copy that last
路径 现在我要到这里
path and now I'm going to go here and go
进入我的
into my uh
终端窗口 我有
terminal window where I've got
能力启动张量奖，也就是
the ability to fire up the tensor award
这些，观众可以在日志
which is these which is the viewer to
运行时实际查看日志，
actually get to view the logs as it runs
我将启动张量板，
I'm going to fire up tensorboard
我要去，我要去，
and I'm gonna gonna and I'm gonna go and
控制点击 localhost 6006 这样它
control click on localhost 6006 so it's
就会打开一个 tensorboard 的视图，
going to open up a view of tensorboard
正如你所看到的，我们已经
and as you can see we're already
开始看到
starting to see the loss average for the
模型实际训练的平均损失，在这里
actual training of the model and here
你可以看到实际
you can see the ramp up of the actual
学习率的上升 在
learning rate over the steps that were
到目前为止完成的步骤中，它有点提高了
done so far so it's kind of ramping up
学习率，它有点让
the learning rate and it kind of
你的耳朵稳定下来，然后
plateaued your ear a little bit then
在那里有点稳定，现在它
kind of plateaued there and now it's got
就像一个大平台，所以我认为它
like a big Plateau so I think it figured
发现这是
out that this is the appropriate
为该模型设置合适的学习率，如果
learning rate for this model and if
一切顺利，它将在
everything goes well it's going to stick
接下来的训练课程中坚持使用该学习率
with that learning rate for the rest of
the training session
，
and
我相信如果您要查看
I believe that if you are to go and look
该学习率的实际值，
at the actual value of that learning
即 uh 2.86 e
rate which is uh 2.86 e minus zero five
uh 文本编码器减零五，单位减去 0
for the uh text encoder and 1.14 minus 0
4，这
4 for the unit this is
几乎是或接近
pretty much the value or close to the
我们作为默认值得到的值，这个
value that we've got as the default this
值是默认值的
one is
两倍，因为我有点
twice as small because I'm kind of
强迫它 通过
forcing it that way through the
hard-coded version of the dynamic
我得到的动态适应的硬编码版本，但这
adaptation that I've got but this is
实际上非常接近我们想要的
actually pretty close to what we want
和我们在默认配置中拥有的，
and what we have in the default
所以这表明
configuration so that goes to show that
默认值
that default value of
0.0001 实际上非常准确 就
0.0001 was actually pretty accurate as
being one of the good training value for
low rows
我们而言，它是低划船的良好训练价值之一，
as far as we are concerned
所以我们需要进行
so we're gonna we're gonna need to go to
650 步，所以我要暂停这个，
650 steps so I'm going to pause this and
让训练完成，然后我们
let the training complete and then we
可以看看 模型的结果
can look at the result of the model
没问题，所以训练刚刚完成，
okay so the training just completed and
正如你所看到的，我们有一个相当不错的
as you can see uh we have a fairly nice
曲线，
curve of
在开始时发生了很多学习，
lots of learning happening at the
学习非常强烈，
beginning learning very strongly and
然后它进入了一个迭代
then it kind of gets into a iteration
阶段，它一直在迭代
phase here where it just keeps iterating
然后迭代，此时它有点好转，
and iterating and it kind of gets better
它有点开始上升了
at this point it kind of started to rise
一点，所以如果
a little bit so what I would kind of if
我要重做这个训练，它可能会
I was to redo this training it would
停止在
probably stop at around
500 或 400 左右，大约 70 步或附近
500 or 400 and sort of 70 steps or near
点所以那是因为在那之后
that point so that's because after that
它似乎有点上升
it seems to kind of Rise a little bit
然后它很漂亮它停止改进它相当
then it pretty it's stopped improving it
开始有点燃烧
pretty started to kind of burn a little
模型在这一点上它已经过度
bit the models at this point it's over
烘烤但是是的这个
baked but yeah this nice downward
向下倾斜的学习率曲线是
sloping learning rate curve here is kind
那种你想看到的，当它像那样
of what you want to see and when it kind
再次上升时，这
of rises again like that that's kind of
表明情况没有
a sign that things are not improving
太大改善，可能模型就像
much and probably the model is just like
在那个时候开始燃烧，但现在让我们看看
starting to burn at that point but now
这个模型是什么
let's have a look at what this model
看起来像
looks like so
um 模型再次保存在这个
um the model was saved again in this
位置作为 White Queen
location as the White Queen
v1.0 所以我将复制它
v1.0 so I'm just going to copy that
并且我们将以稳定的扩散进入这里
and we're gonna go here in stable
diffusion
um 我还有另一个视频我刚刚
um and I've had another video I just
完成并且 然后录制并
completed and then recorded and
发布在 YouTube 上，但我们将
published on YouTube but we're going to
利用相同的提示，我们
leverage that same prompt and we're just
将用
going to replace the Laura that was in
我们刚刚创建的新提示替换旧提示中的劳拉，
this old one with the new one that we
just created
所以白皇后和我要接受
so the White Queen and I'm gonna take
这里的实际标记或
the actual token here or the trigger
我应该说的触发词并将其作为
word I should say and put that as the
触发词放在后面这样它会触发
trigger word after such that it triggers
整个模型然后让我们确保
the whole model and then let's make sure
那里没有任何东西会把
there's nothing in there that would kind
事情分开好吧大胆的
of break things apart okay kind of bold
红唇她不会 已经建好了，
red lips she doesn't have already built
所以我们要
so we're just gonna go and take out the
red lips
在这里拿出红唇版本，嗯，
version here uh
我猜苗条的身体戴着鹅卵石，
um I guess slim body wearing a pebble
我们真的不想改变我们的
well we don't really want to change our
地址，我们想看看她是否会
address we want to see if she's going to
一起来 她
come with her
标准的白色女王礼服，我们
standard white queen dress and we can
可以在它之后把它放回去，看看
potentially put it back after it and see
我们是否可以像她的实际礼服一样改变，
if we can change like her actual dress
或者如果模型太僵硬以至于
or if the model is so rigid that it's
不允许我们那样做，
not going to allow us to do that
好吧，所以我认为这很好呃
okay so I think that's pretty good uh
一切 其他都很好所以让我们
everything else is fine so let's give it
试一试让我们
a try let's generate
在花园里生成四张白皇后的照片
four pictures of the White Queen in a
garden
希望我们能得到好的
and hopefully we're gonna get good
结果到目前为止我还不知道它看起来
results I don't know so far it looks
很不错啊
pretty good
是的看起来像我们的
ah yeah that looks like our
我猜 正如你所看到的那样，花园
and I guess the garden as you can see
吸收了很多
it's picking up a lot of the look and
图像的外观和感觉，嗯，这是
feel of the image that uh was the
电影的坐姿，嗯，
sitting for the movie
um
很多这些图像，所以它
so a lot of those image so what does it
看起来是什么，那张脸看起来很棒，
look over that one is looking great the
但那是因为它是 有点
face but that's because it's kind of a
小，嗯，是的，
small smallish piece uh yeah that one
看起来不错，看起来
looks pretty good
不错，这张地球的脸
looking good this one Earth face is a
有点奇怪，但我们可以尝试
little weird but that we could try
像我
something like the what I was showing up
在另一个
in the other
视频中出现的东西，让我们把它发送给群众演员，让我们把
video let's send that to extras let's
分辨率提高一倍 那一张
double up the resolution of that one
图片所以一张图片我们只是
image so a single image we're just gonna
用swin IR加倍
double up with swin IR
好吧所以让我们运行它然后
okay so let's run it
一旦它加倍我将把
and then once it's doubled I'm going to
它发送到油漆中我们将
send it to in paint and we're going to
看看
see
我们是否真的可以修复 脸部以
if we can actually fix the face in a
正确的方式，所以现在我得到了图像
right way so now I've got the image what
我要去我想做的是回到
I'm going what I want to do is go back
这里发送这张照片，这是一个不好的
here send this picture which is the bad
油漆现在我们有所有
one to in paint now we have all of the
关于劳拉的文字和
text about the Laura and the config
那里的配置，我想回到额外的部分
there and I want to go back into extras
并拍下那张并排照片并将
and take that abreast picture and send
其发送到窗格中，这样它将取代
it to in pane so it's going to replace
我们拥有的那个版本，但具有
that version that we had but with the
双分辨率版本，现在我
double resolution version and now I'm
将进入
just going to go in
面具 我们想要在油漆中处理的脸
mask the face that we want to sort of in
paint
可能会更好，
it may be a better one
好吧，我要去这里
okay and I'm going to go here and make
确保我们有 512 x 512 的
sure we have 512 by 512 resolution for
渲染分辨率，所以我们只遮盖了这
the rendering so we only masked that's
很好我们要给它一些
fine we're going to give it some mean
重新创建的平均方式所以让我们尝试生成
way to recreate so let's try to generate
一张新面孔，看看模型是否
a new face and see if the model is good
足够好，让
enough to get us a better face indeed
我们得到一张
when the faces so now we have a much
更好的面孔
much better face compared to what we
在
used to have here if you look at the
原来的脸上很糟糕如果你看看
original face pretty bad if you look at
新的彩绘脸更好我们
the new in painted face much better we
甚至可以尝试生成一个新版本
could even try to generate a new version
只是为了看看我们是否可以得到更好的东西
just to see if we could get something
even better
就像测试一样是的
just as a test
确实我们有两个很像
and yeah indeed we have a much like the
以前的面孔非常好所以
two previous faces were pretty good so
现在我们有一个更好的版本所以
now we have a much better version so
这就是你如何再次快速修复看起来
that's how again you can quickly fix a
有点奇怪的面孔
face that kind of looks a little weird
并修复它我们甚至可以尝试修复
and fix it and we could even try to fix
这个我不知道它是否会继续
this one I don't know if it's going to
工作，但如果我们真的想尝试，
work but like if we wanted to really try
我们可以去发送它，将
we could go and send it extra
分辨率提高一倍，将
double up the resolution
其发送到油漆中，去除，在脸上放置一个
send that to in paint remove that put a
合适的面具，
proper mask around the face for this one
让我们确保我们有 512 x 512
and let's make sure we have 512 by 512
让我们看看如何 我们可以更好地改善那张脸
let's see how we could improve that face
much better
所以现在我们在那个角色上有更好的脸
so now we have a better face on that
所以是的所以我认为那个模型
character so yeah so I think that model
呃看起来还不错呃我认为这
is uh looking not so bad uh I think it's
又是Gan可能有点
again the Gan might be a little bit too
太强了因为我认为它给出了 一张
strong because I think it gives like a
脸看起来有点太干净了，
little bit too clean looking of a face
但其他一切看起来都很好，比如
but everything else looks very good like
珍珠项链晚上的头发
the the pearl necklace the hair evening
很棒，我想我们只需要让
is awesome I think we just need to get
那张
that
脸不那么完美，
face a little less perfect
所以再说一次，这不是一个坏瓶子，它
so again that's not a bad bottle it may
实际上可能很好 在某些情况下，
actually be good in some occasions to
有一个模型可以产生如此完美的面孔，
have a model that produces perfect faces
看起来非常干净，但
like that like so very clean looking but
我想这可能不是每个人的脸，所以要
I guess it may not be to everyone's face
解决这个问题，那就要重新运行
so to fix that then it would be to rerun
Gan 清理，但 Lesser
the Gan cleanup but with the Lesser
strike 可能会达到 50% 而不是
strike maybe at 50 percent instead of a
全力以赴 现在让我们看看我们是否
full strength and now let's see if we
真的能让她穿另一件
can actually get her to wear a different
衣服 所以如果我们去说穿
dress so if we go and say a wearing a
头饰 穿 Peplum 裙子
headlam a Peplum dress
不管它意味着什么 所以让我们试试吧 让我们
whatever it means so let's try it and
看看这是否真的能让
let's see if that would actually enable
我们 改变模型，让我们
us to change the model and let's
看看就颜色而言，它看起来相当僵硬，
let's see it looks fairly rigid as far
因为据了解
as the color goes because it's learned
她现在穿的是白色的，这件衣服
that she's wearing white now the dress
看起来
looks slightly different
与她平时穿的那件略有不同，
from the one that she's usually wearing
嗯，
um
但是再次骑自行车，他们都真的
but again the biking them all really
真的知道了一件衣服
really learned that one dress
并且很难让它
and it's going to be very difficult to
忘记那个
make it forget about that one so
所以是的，
yeah it's uh
我认为我们真的
I think we really learned the look of
通过衣服，
the character with the dress and with
发型和面部化妆等等了解了角色的外观，
the hairstyle and with the face makeup
我想你可以在
and whatnot uh I guess as you can see
这里看到 这些角色都没有
here none of these characters have a
皇冠我们所做的美丽是
crown the beauty of what we've done is
内部应该能够看到白
interior should be able to see the White
皇后我现在可以说皇冠
Queen I could say crown
应该创造出
now that should create image of the
戴着皇冠的白皇后的形象因为
White Queen wearing a crown because the
劳拉应该根据
Laura should have learned based on the
说明皇冠是什么意思，是
captioning what Crown means and yep
的，现在当我们使用提示调用皇冠时，她确实戴着她的皇冠，
indeed now she's wearing her crown when
we invoke the crown using
the prompt
我们甚至可以尝试
and we could even go as far as trying to
索要一把剑，除非只有
ask for a sword unless there's only like
三四张图片实际上是一把剑的
three or four picture where a sword was
标题，所以我 我不确定
actually captioned so I'm not sure if
它是否会做得很好，
it's gonna do a very good job
但如果我们看一下所有这些，
but if we look at all of those the
实际模型实际上非常
actual model is pretty actually pretty
好，我的意思
good I mean the quality
是质量非常好，它
is pretty darn good it's very it's
看起来很像电影中的照片
looking a lot like the pictures uh of
和 让我们试着要一把
the movie and let's try to ask for a
剑，
sword
让我们看看这
and let's see if that's going to work I
don't know
can we get er to wear her crown with a
sword
in her hands
he could kind of tries to do that maybe
是否有效
there is where there was not enough
她拿着剑的照片，所以
pictures of her holding a sword so it's
有点尝试，
kind of trying it
但效果很差
but it's doing a pretty bad job about it
所以并不感到惊讶，因为
so not surprised because there was so
图像太少了，嗯，所以剑的东西
few image uh yeah so the sword thing is
很好，她拿着剑时没有戴
well she was not wearing a crown when
皇冠 所以从理论上讲，通过
she was holding a sword so in theory by
移除王冠我们可以获得
removing the crown we might be able to
更好的结果
get better results
是的，我很好奇这是否会
yeah I'm curious to see if that would
奏效
work
剑会更好，
the sword is going to come out better
因为我们不再为
now that we are not fighting with the
我们想要王冠和
fact that we want a crown and the sword
一系列图片中的剑
in a series of pictures that were never
现在从未见过即使没有王冠也没有用呃做那么好的工作
seen now didn't do that great of a job
with the uh even without the crown
但它让你清楚地知道
but it gives you an idea uh clearly that
模型
model didn't have enough enough swords
在呃数据集中没有足够的剑来 正确地了解
in the uh data set to properly learn
上下文中的剑是什么，但它
what the sword is in the context but it
给你一点
kind of gives you a hint of
剑的暗示，所以你可以看到它是以
of a sword so you can see that it was
一种奇怪的方式学习的，
learned in in a weird way but it was
但无论如何我希望你们发现
learned so anyway I hope you guys found
这很有趣，那就是 你
this uh interesting and that's how you
如何创建一个家，如果你
can create a home and if you're
感兴趣，我可能会发布
interested I'm gonna probably publish
我刚刚在 civit AI 上做的那个模型，
that exact model that I just did here on
我会把链接
civit AI and I'm going to put the link
放在 YouTube 视频的描述中，
in the description of the YouTube video
这样你就可以去 尝试玩它，
so you can go and try to play with it
呃，再见，
and uh enjoy
伙计们
bye guys